Contacts

+38(095)5364942

inna.forkert@gmail.com

LinkedIn

<u>Telegram</u>

WhatsApp

GitHub

Portfolio

Kyiv, Ukraine

Expertise

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- React
- Redux
- Vue
- HTML
- CSS, SCSS
- Node
- Git, GitHub

Languages

- English advanced
- German upper

intermediate

Ukrainian - native

Inna Forkert

Full Stack Developer

3+ months and ongoing commercial experience (Vue, Node, React). Lucky IT-Generation grant winner. Fluent in English and decent German level. Several projects (games, landings, applications), which you are welcome to check out in my portfolio. Team player, problem-solver, hardworking and perseverant.

Experience

Q January 2023 - now

Upwork

Junior Vue Developer

Working part-time in a team on a commercial project. My tasks include creating new functionalities and reworking existing ones. Technologies used are mainly Vue, Laravel, SCSS.

• February 2023 - April 2023 (5 weeks)

Unicorn

Intern Full Stack Developer

Ended up being top-1 candidate for hire (not hired because of budget redistribution) with 93% total score (35% more than average). Worked in a team with business-analyst and successfully completed a project using fresh-learned technology. Met all deadlines and requirements.

February 2021 - November 2022

Sumy State University

Teacher

Taught foreign students from more than 20 countries for more than 1000 hours in English. Co-authored a textbook in Endocrinology in Ukrainian and English. Claimed a patent for better sonography use in research.

Education

O September 2014 - November 2022

Sumy State University Medicine Masters' Degree, Internship

O September 2022 - February 2023

GoIT

GolT Frontend Development Bootcamp